Man, I've been so stiff lately.
Then shall I give you a massage?
You can do that?
Yeah, that's it. That feels incredible.
I was designed to soothe my master.
I can do erotic massages as well,
but that's locked behind master registration—
Nope! A normal one's fine!
Am I really so unworthy?
Do you...
Do you hate me, Master?
She's busting out the tears! I must resist!
It's not that. You're just too human-like.
Look, registering as your master
would make me your owner, right?
But I can't treat you like property
when you look like a human girl.
Then how am I supposed to serve you?
Saying you're human-like is a compliment!
You're not useless.
And besides,
sex is something that two humans do together!
Master!
I mean, not that I know much about love or sex.
I've never dated or been in a physical relationship.
The most I've done is hold hands.
Anyway, I just think
that we should start as friends first.
You want to be my friend, Master?
Please don't call me "Master."
Then what do I call you?
Oh. Um...
My...
My name is fine.
Akane.
May I kiss you?
Where did that come from?!
You got upset when I suddenly kissed you last time.
I don't quite get it.
I mean, I kiss her every morning.
Akane.
I love you, Akane.
I knew it.
I can't say no.
Akane.
Akane. Akane.
I love you, Akane.
When she whispers my name like that,
it's like she's my girlfriend.
Would you please make me feel good, too?
Nadeshiko,
you're trying to make me register, aren't you?
I knew it! You are!
I can't let my guard down with you.
I just... I'm sorry.
Are you mad at me, Akane?
Nadeshiko, can you feel pain?
Sort of. I'm programmed to avoid damage.
I see.
I would've felt awful if I'd hurt her.
I'd love to do more sometime, Akane.
Hearing her say my name is sweet agony.